（警察局证物保管处）
（案件编号：22408 | 状态：未结案）
你好
Hello.
嘿 我马上就到了 别忘记了带钱
Hey, I'm on my way, and don't forget my money.
待会见 贝利 难道你忘了
See you soon. And, Bailey, don't you forget…
妈的
Shit…
好奇会害死猫的哦
Curiosity killed the cat!
死你妹
Shit…
（献给贝利）
我操
Jesus…
真酷
Cool.
好了 你好啊 亲爱的
Well, hello, dolly.
《鬼娃回魂4：鬼娃新娘》
（疯狂杀手蕾于芝加哥玩具店被射杀）
（杀人狂终于毙命）
（疯狂杀手遭遇枪杀）
（男孩宣称娃娃被杀手的灵魂附身）
你好 我是金凯德警探 杰德的叔叔
Hello. I'm Chief Kincaid, Jade's uncle.
大卫·柯林斯 幸会 先生
David Collins. Nice to meet you, sir.
进来吧 大卫
David, come on in.
杰德 大卫来了
Jade, David's here.
嗯 杰德一直对你赞不绝口 大卫
Well, I've been hearing good things about you, David.
我还知道你明年秋天要去普林斯顿
I understand you're off to Princeton next fall.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
主修什么？
What are you going to study?
戏剧
Theater Arts.
嗯 还拿过运动奖学金 对不？是曲棍球么？
Mmm-hmm. But on an athletic scholarship, right? Playing hockey?
花样滑冰
Figure skating.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
杰德
Jade!
沃伦 别大喊大叫
Warren, don't scream.
嗨
Hi.
你看起来好美
You look great.
杰德 我必须叮嘱你
Jade, I have to tell you.
这家伙比你上一任优秀多了
This guy is a big improvement over the last one.
我想你父母一定会支持你的
I think your mother and father would have agreed.
我的朋友他们都喜欢
My parents liked all my friends.
午夜之前回来
I'll be home by midnight.
我会照顾她的 先生
She's in good hands, sir.
呃
Uh…
是不是忘了什么？
You forget something?
哦
Oh.
这是送你的
This is for you.
我喜欢百合花
I love lilies.
实际上 这是一种兰花 春草兰
Actually, it's an orchid. Cymbidium orchid.
花瓶里放点水和阿司匹林
You put it in a vase and drop an aspirin in the water,
它就能在花瓶里开上一整个星期
it should last you the whole week.
从书上看的
Oh so I read.
幸会幸会
Nice meeting you.
她刚出门
She just left.
你好漂亮
You look beautiful.
- 就这么骗过沃伦了？- 嗯嗯…
- So Warren fell for it? - Mmm-hmm.
大卫让他印象深刻 我想他是爱上了大卫
David made quite an impression. I think Warren's in love.
拉倒吧 不是我的菜 我可对制服诱惑没感觉
Yuck. Not my type.I'm so over that whole uniform thing.
我现在不会回家 妈妈你别开玩笑了
* I won't go home now, mama Don't make a fool of me *
你听 我在唱着布基伍基的歌
* You see, I am the boogie-woogie *
要命了 是尼德莱诺斯
Christ. It's Needlenose.
抓到了哈
Gotcha.
（傻瓜巫术大全）
[咒语]
我祈求你 赐予我力量吧
Give me the power, I beg of you.
[咒语]
我祈求你 赐予我力量吧
Give me the power, I beg of you.
[咒语]
苏醒吧
Awake.
Awake!
苏醒吧 苏醒吧 苏醒吧 苏醒吧
Awake! Awake! Awake! Awake!
什么破书
What a crock.
嘿 蒂凡尼
Hey, Tiffany.
你在这干嘛？
What are you doing here?
别这样 让我进去 我都快冻死了
Come on. Let me in. I'll catch my death out here.
进来吧 进来吧
Promises, promises.
哇喔 唔
Whoa. Whoo…
嘿 今天过的咋样？
Hey, how was your day?
老样子 老样子
Same old, same old.
- 嘿 看看这个 - 啥玩意？
- Hey, check it out. - What?
看看
Check it out.
什么玩意？
What is it?
你该说 这是谁？
You mean, Who is it?
这是谁？
Who is it?
确切说 那曾经是谁？
You mean, Who was it?
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
哦 我的天啊 你在他身上可真是煞费苦心啊 是吧？
Oh, my God. You really did a number on him, didn't you?
你当时用的什么？当时真的这么血腥么？
What did you use? Was it really bloody?
他当时尖叫了么？惨不惨
Did he scream a lot? Was he half…
你知道么 达米安 这家伙看起来真他妈的面熟
You know, Damien, this guy looks awfully familiar.
我能认出他的指甲油
I recognize the nail polish.
妈的
Shit.
你根本就没有杀人 对不对？
You never really actually Killed anybody, did you?
是不是？是不是？你这个可怜虫
Did you? Did you? You pathetic worm!
别这样 蒂凡尼 我正在努力呢
Come on, Tiff. I'm working up to it.
哦 得了吧
Oh, man.
你知道吗 弄这个东西我花了十个小时
You know, it took me 10 hours to make that thing.
达米安
Damien.
什么事？
Yeah?
能不能帮帮忙 帮我看看口红是不是掉沙发底下了
Could you do me a favor, and see if my lipstick is under the sofa there?
啊哈 啊哈 啊哈
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah…
不要起来 往前爬
Back on your knees. Crawl.
真听话
Good boy.
就这样呆在地板上面别起来
Stay down on the floor where you belong.
就这样
That's right.
这下面什么都没有
There's nothing under here.
夏洛特
Charlotte.
你怎么跑出来的？
How did you get out?
哦
Oh!
呃
Ugh!
蒂凡尼？
Tiffany?
你看 现在就我俩
Well, here we are.
我俩拍拖多长时间了 啊？
How long have we been going out for now, huh?
什么？
What?
难道你不认为你让我等太久了么？
Don't you think you've kept me waiting long enough?
没有
No.
哦
Oh.
你知道法国人怎么形容高潮么？
You know what the French call an orgasm?
濒临死亡
The little death.
来吧 蒂凡尼 让我们来体验濒死的快感吧
Come on, Tiffany. Let's die a little.
啊哈
Ah!
嗨 我是恰吉 想玩玩么？
Hi. I'm Chucky. Wanna play?
你这玩意儿他妈的从哪弄来的？
Where the hell did you get this thing?
从条子手里整来的
Got him from the cops.
是个真实的杀人娃娃 我把它缝好了
He's the actual doll from those murders. I stitched him together.
你和我开玩笑呢吧
You got to be kidding me.
不 我没开玩笑
No, I'm not kidding you.
- 我为什么要开玩笑？- 得了吧 蒂凡尼
- Why would I kid you? - Come on, Tiffany.
- 我知道你很迷信 - 我不迷信
- I knew you were obsessed.- I'm not…
- 但是这个恰吉？他太过时了吧？- 不它没过时
- But Chucky? He's so '80s. - No, he's not.
- 它一点都不吓人 - 不 它很吓人
- He isn't even scary. - Yes, he is.
看看他 你看什么呢 哥们？让你盯着我看
Look at him. What are you looking at, punk? You looking at me?
好吧 那么 算我错了吧
All right. So, I was wrong.
我一开始以为它是个很有意思的娃娃
I thought he'd make an interesting toy.
- 达米安？- 啊？
- Damien? - Huh?
想玩玩么？
You wanna play?
好吧
Okay.
首先呢 先拷起来
First, I do this.
准备好玩「三人行」了么？
Are you ready for a ménage a trois?
那是啥啊？
What's that?
我以为你懂法语呢
I thought you understood French.
哇哦
Ow!
瞧好吧
Now you watch me…
你们俩都瞧好了
Both of you.
你知道么 达米安 关于恰吉我还有些事没和你说
You know, Damien, there's something I never told you about Chucky.
别告诉我这个娃娃是个会尿裤子的蠢蛋
Don't tell me Schmucky is one of those dolls who wets his pants.
啊哈 啊哈 啊哈 假如我是你 我就不会那样说恰吉
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah… I wouldn't talk that way about Chucky if I were you.
他的脾气 很火爆哦
He has a very bad temper.
哦
Ooh!
你知道吗 我们同居好多年了
You see, we lived together for years.
当然 那是在条子杀死他之前的事
Of course, that was before the cops killed him.
在他被乱枪打死 附身变成娃娃之前
That was before he passed his soul into that doll there.
哥们 他曾经非常的爱吃醋
Boy, was he ever jealous.
只要有人看我一眼 恰吉就会去修理他的
Anybody even looked at me, Chucky would take care of him.
你会吧 恰吉？
Wouldn't you, Chucky?
我们当时都要结婚了
We were gonna get married.
天啊 当时他真是个完美性伴侣
God, was he an incredible lover.
是操过我的男人中最棒的一个
He was the best I ever had.
得了吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.
就他那个小鸡鸡能满足你这样的悍妇？
He ain't big enough to take care of a woman like you?
混蛋 鸡巴的尺寸不重要 重要的是怎么个干法
It ain't the size that counts, asshole. It's what you do with it.
就是这样子
All right.
嗨
Hi.
感觉咋样？
How you been?
很好
Okay.
- 你呢？- 好得很
- You? - Peachy.
事实上 和你说实话吧 我都有点手生了
Actually, to tell you the truth, I've been kind of out of it.
我懂的 我找你找了十年
I know. It took me 10 years to find you.
真恶心
That is sick.
和这种垃圾选手混有啥前途？
What are you doing with this jerk anyway?
十年是一段很长的时间 恰吉
Ten years is a long time, Chucky.
还有 我从没和他上过床 你知道我的
Besides, I was never actually with him.You know me.
我杀人不眨眼 但是我只和心爱的人上床
I'll kill anybody, but I'll only sleep with someone I love.
你看着好美 蒂凡尼
You look great, Tiff.
谢谢
Thanks.
我是认真的 实话实说
I mean it. I gotta be honest.
我总认为你会就此而放纵自己
I always thought you were gonna let yourself go.
过来
Come here.
好的
Yeah.
啊？
Huh?
别摸了
Stop it.
嗯.
Hmm.
满意了吗？
Are you satisfied?
- 请问我能上车里等着吗？- 不行
- Can I wait in the car, please? - No.
好了 小痞子 该你了
All right, Boogie Nights, you're up.
这真是他妈的胡搞
This is such a load of shit.
你知道我们没喝过酒
You know we haven't been drinking.
那么 你们现在就没什么好担心的了 是不？
Well, then you've got nothing to worry about, do you?
晚上好 警长
Evening, Chief.
看来是虚惊一场吗
Seems like a false alarm here.
没事了 诺顿 安全第一 对不？
That's okay, Norton.Better safe than sorry, right?
你越来越过分了
This is a new low.
你也是
For you, too.
- 滚进车里 - 你管我
- Get in the car. - Bite me.
杰德 等你到十八了 你就算下地狱我也不管
Jade, when you're 18, you can go to hell, for all I care.
但是在那之前 我要盯紧你
But until then, I'm stuck with you.
但是如果你和这人渣让我难堪 我就会让你好看
And I'll be damned if I'm gonna let you embarrass me
你和这人渣到此为止了
by ending up on Jerry Springerwith some trailer trash lowlife.
操你妈的
You fuck.
但是你操不成
But you won't.
远离杰德 永远
Not Jade anyway.Not anymore.
上车
In the car.
你不能阻止我们见面的
You can't keep us from seeing each other.
我是警长 我可以为所欲为
I'm the Chief of Police, sport. I can do whatever I want.
所以呢 例如 我今晚就可以给你验血
So if, for example, I was to run a blood test on you tonight,
那结果就会让你好看 显示你嗑药了
and the results made you look like
人在江湖 身不由己啊
Christian Slater on New Year's Eve,
你认为有人会质疑我么？
you think anybody would question me?
- 唬谁呢？- 走着瞧
- He's bluffing? - Try me.
我真希望我们能白头偕老
I wish we really could choose our own families.
大卫 你的小兰花现在枯萎了 听懂了么？
David, you keep your orchid dry now, you hear?
走吧 亲爱的
Come on, sunshine.
「走着瞧」
"Try me"
去他的
Screw him.
换做是我 我就会带杰德私奔 远走高飞
If I were you, I would take Jade, get the hell out of Dodge,
再也不回来
and never look back.
看 恰吉 我做的瑞士肉丸 你的最爱
Look, Chucky.I made Swedish meatballs, your favorite.
亲爱的 你太费心了
Honey, you shouldn't have.
是吗 我希望今晚的一切都会很完美
Well, I wanted everything tonight to be absolutely perfect.
蒂凡尼 那他妈的是啥？
Tiff, what the hell is that?
宝宝护栏 给婴儿用的
It's a playpen, silly, for the nursery.
你知道吗 恰吉 戒指我还带着
You know, Chucky, I still have the ring.
- 什么戒指？- 就那个 你留给我的那个
- What ring? - The ring, the one you left for me.
你死的那天 我在壁炉里找到的
I found it on the mantel the night you were killed.
我一直都没摘下过
I've never taken it off.
哦 那个啊？我从维维安·范佩尔特身上弄的那个
Oh, that? The one I got from Vivian Van Pelt.
谁是维维安？
Vivian who?
维维安·范佩尔特
Vivian Van Pelt.
她被我弃尸入河了 想起来了？
I dumped her in the river, remember?
这戒指能值个五六千吧 至少
That ring is worth five or six grand, easy!
你是说 你当时没打算向我求婚？
You mean, you weren't gonna ask me to marry you?
你他妈的刚才 说啥？
What are you…fucking nuts?
你以为我
You thought…
你一点都没变
You haven't changed.
以后也不会变
You'll never change.
我他妈的当时到底在想些啥？
What the hell was I thinking?
现在 先把我从这娃娃身体里弄出去
Now, the first thing we gotta do is get me out of this body
永远的出去
once and for all.
不行
No.
我想我更喜欢你现在的样子
I think I prefer you like this.
有点小可爱 就好像一个小宝宝
You're kind of cute. You're just like a little baby.
小宝宝痒不痒啊？痒不痒？
Is the little baby ticklish? Is he?
别闹了
Stop!
痒不痒啊？痒不痒啊？痒不痒啊？
Is he? Is he? Is he?
别闹 别闹了
Stop! Stop!
痒不痒啊？痒不痒啊？
Is he? Is he?
好了 妈咪累了
Okay. Mommy's tired.
该睡觉了
Time to go to sleep.
好了 我想通了
Okay, I get it.
你现在还纠结着关于结婚成家的事
You're still hung up on the domestic thing.
没问题 我们会搭上末班车的
No problem. We'll get hitched.
抱歉 我对小个子不来电
Sorry. I'm not into short guys.
我妈妈总说爱会让人自由
My mother always said love was supposed to set you free.
但其实不是那样 恰吉
But that's not true, Chucky.
我一直被你的爱禁锢着 禁锢了好久
I've been a prisoner of my love for you for a very long time.
现在是还债的时候了
Now it's payback time.
赶紧放我出去
You let me out of here right now!
做个好梦 混蛋
Sweet dreams, asshole.
我痴狂了
* I'm crazy *
痴狂于这惆怅的爱
* Crazy for feelin' so blue *
早已明白
* I knew *
虽然你说爱我天长地久
* You'd love me as long as you wanted *
但是某一天
* And someday *
你还是会离我而去另寻新欢
* You'd leave me for somebody new *
为相思而痴狂
* Crazy for tryin'*
为哭泣而痴狂
* And crazy for cryin' *
还依然痴狂的爱着你
* And I'm crazy for lovin' you *
我为相思而痴狂
* I'm crazy for tryin'*
为哭泣而痴狂
* And crazy for cryin' *
杰西 亲爱的 能帮个忙么？
Jesse, honey, could you give me a hand with this?
行 好的 等一会
Yeah, okay, just a second.
谢谢 小心肝 欠你一次哦
Thanks, sweetface. I owe you one.
呃…
Yeah…
该死
Shit!
嘿
Hi.
看来 你要搬出来？
So, you moving out already?
还没那么走运
No such luck.
哦 抱歉
Oh, sorry.
想让我把它放进那辆车里？
You want me to put that in the car?
是的 我只是 你知道的 拿去捐点东西行行善么
Yeah, I'm just, you know, taking some stuff to the Goodwill.
好重啊
It's heavy.
恩 是的
Oh, yeah.
里面装的啥啊？
What do you got in here?
哦 你知道的 装点这 装点那
Oh, you know. A little of this, a little of that.
一些快过时的东西 全是
Stuff that's gone out of style. Yeah.
你也看见过捐赠品
You ever look at something,
你也知道有些东西看到会恶心到死
and you realize you are just sick to death looking at it?
我对这箱子就有这种感觉
That's how I feel about that shit.
放这 扔车里
Here. In the trunk.
扔车里？
In the trunk?
你行的
You can do it.
膝盖弯一下
Bend your knees.
哇喔 你太强了 肌肉不错 经常锻炼？
Wow. You are strong. Nice muscle tone. You work out a lot?
经常做俯卧撑
I've been doing some push-ups.
抱歉
Sorry.
没事 没事
No, that's okay.
也死不了 还能帮点忙
Can't hurt it. Might help.
蒂凡尼 你丫死哪去了？
Tiffany, where the fuck are you?
你有朋友？
You got some company?
不 带孩子呢 小屁孩嘴不干净
No, just babysitting. Foul-mouthed little fucker.
我帮你绑上吧
Let me help you with this.
那么 你等会干什么？
So, what are you doing later on?
因为我在想
'Cause I was thinking
或许我俩「出去喝一杯」什么的
maybe you and I could go get a drink or something?
就是 如果你想去的话
That is, if you're up to it.
不 不 不去了
No, no. I can't.
为嘛啊？
Why?
我有女朋友了
I'm seeing someone.
真的吗？
Really?
好男人都死光了
All the good guys are taken.
我得走了
I gotta go.
好的
Okay.
拜拜
Bye.
杰西？
Jesse?
好好待她 杰西
Treat her right, Jesse.
什么？
Excuse me?
要好好待她 千万别逢场作戏 虚情假意
Treat her right. Never take her for granted.
好像我妈妈也总这么说
It's like my mother always used to say,
「女人整天为男人在灶前忙碌」
"A woman spends all day slaving over a hot stove for a man,
「男人至少也得为女人洗个碗嘛」
"the least he can do is the dishes"
我妈也算是半个哲学家了 至少
She's kind of a philosopher, my mother.
嗯
Hmm.
慢点开
Take it easy.
再见
See you around.
（慢慢整死蒂凡尼）
拼写：女人
Spell "woman."
B-I-T-C-H.BITCH.（婊子 贱人）
B-I-T-C-H.BITCH.
错误 女人的正确拼法是
That is incorrect. The correct spelling of "woman" is
W-O-M-A-N
W-O-M-A-N.
看看你还会些什么
Shows how much you know.
呦吼 我回来了
Yoo-hoo! I'm home.
哦 啧 啧 啧 啧 啧
Oh! Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk…
如果你不好好玩 我可就把玩具都收走了
If you can't play nice, I may just have to take your toys away.
有个惊喜给你哦
I have a surprise for you.
我一直在考虑你说的关于结婚的事
I've been thinking about what you said about wanting to get married.
- 是吗？- 我认为最好还是先把你安定下来
- Yeah? - I think it would do you good to settle down.
宝贝 这样很好
Babe, this is great.
我敢肯定 你不会后悔的
You won't regret it, I promise.
我会像公主一样的对待你
I'm gonna treat you like a princess.
那是啥？
What's that?
你的新娘
Your bride.
戴上戒指 我俩结婚
With this ring, I thee wed.
哦 恰吉 她很漂亮
Oh, Chucky.She's beautiful.
你丫死定了
You are so dead.
恭喜恭喜 恰吉
Congratulations, Chucky.
现在 我想你们两个小孩子想亲热一下
Now, I'm sure you two kids would want to be alone.
关于警员鲍勃·贝利的凶手线索仍然毫无头绪
While there are still no leads in the murder of Officer Bob Bailey,
但是种种迹象表明
evidence suggests that his death maybe
与今日发现的另一起命案有关
linked to another body found earlier today.
原名为霍华德·菲茨沃特的达米安·贝洛克
Damien Baylock, whose real name was Howard Fitzwater,
于今日下午发现被弃尸东河
was dragged from the East River this afternoon.
普雷斯顿警探 你认为两起凶杀案有关系么？
Detective Preston, is there a connection between these two murders?
有可能 我们正在侦破中
Could be. Possibly. We're looking into it.
像是连环杀手所为么？
Is this the work of a serial killer?
- 也许吧 - 我可没这么说
- Maybe. - I didn't say that.
是的 长官 你没这么说 但是你可以给我们分析下罪犯的心理
No, sir, you didn 't, but what can you tell us about these murders?
分析个屁
Nothing.
我可以告诉你这里曾经是
I can tell you that this used to be
一个很漂亮 安宁的乡下农场
a nice, quiet, rural community.
她还活着 活着
She's alive! Alive!
弗兰肯斯坦的新娘
The bride of Frankenstein.
我誓爱到底 永守贞洁 至死方休
I promise to love, honor and cherish till death do us part.
说的真对
You got that right.
她厌烦于我
She hate me.
我们非死不可
We belong dead.
[咒语]
我祈求你 赐予我力量吧
Give me the power, I beg of you.
[咒语]
苏醒吧
Awake!
什么破咒语
What a crock.
我去你妈的 你对我做了什么？
You son of a bitch! What have you done to me?
你如愿以偿了 你现在是我的了 亲爱的
You got your wish. You're mine now, doll.
还有你知道这有多好么？
And if you know what's good for you?
你将会去相爱 并永守贞洁
you are going to love, honor and obey.
我不会嫁给你这个小玩偶娃娃的
I wouldn't marry you if you had the body of G.l. Joe.
嘿 土娃娃 也不去照照镜子
Hey, Raggedy Ann, you looked in the mirror lately?
现在根本就不是你抱怨的时候
Now is not the time to get picky. Hmm.
（傻瓜巫术大全）
面对吧 蒂凡尼 没有我帮你 你会一直这个样子的
Face it, Tiff. You need me. Otherwise, you're stuck like this for good.
不用你管 我自己查咒语
I don't need you. I'll look it up myself.
好吧 查吧 第六章
Oh, go ahead. Chapter six.
217页
Page 217.
洛阿神之心 什么玩意？
The Heart of Damballa. What's that?
一个护身符
An amulet.
有了它 才能向人类身体中移魂
We need it to transfer our souls into human bodies.
啊 哪能找到呢？
Okay. And where the hell is it?
那些混蛋向我开枪的那晚
I was wearing it around my neck
我就把它带在我的脖子上
the night those bastards gunned me down.
它现在和我的尸体一起埋在 新泽西洲 哈肯萨克市
It was buried with my corpse in Hackensack, New Jersey.
好吧 我们出发吧
All right, let's go.
哦 当然 我控制方向盘你来踩油门
Oh, sure. I'll steer and you can work the pedals.
我们是娃娃啊 你个白痴
We're dolls, you dope!
哦 天啊 那我们怎么办？
Oh, my God! What are we gonna do?
闭嘴
Shut up.
你闭嘴
You shut up.
我不明白 为啥不邮寄娃娃呢？
I don't get it. Why don't you just mail the dolls?
这些娃娃很特别的
These dolls are very special.
有什么「特别」的
What do you mean, "special"?
我是说 如果明天你送到了
I mean, there's$500 in it for you
就有500元报酬
if you get them there by tomorrow.
别问太多
No questions asked.
我本可以自己做的
I'd do it myself,
但是我得照顾我的一个智障小屁孩
but I have to take care of a friend who's mentally incapacitated.
好吧
Yeah.
好吧 我去做
Yeah, I'll do it.
但是我要一千元
But I want$1, 000.
好的 小心肝 我会先预付一半
Okay, sweetface, I can give you half now,
然后我新泽西的朋友会给你另一半的
and my friend in Jersey will give you the rest.
钥匙就在垫子下面
Keys are under the mat.
为我画上你的浓妆吧 宝贝
* Color me your color, baby *
为我画上你的浓妆吧
* Color me your color *
为我画上你的浓妆吧 宝贝
* Color me your color, darlin'*
我深知你心
* I know who you are *
卸掉你那浓浓的伪装
* Come up off your color chart *
我知道你来自哪里
* I know where you're coming from *
约我吧 约我吧
* Call me Call me *
一直都在线
* On the line *
约我吧 随时随地都约我吧
* Call me, call me any, anytime *
约我吧 约我吧
* Call me Call me *
亲爱的 无论白昼黑夜都可以随时约我
* My love, you can call me any day or night *
约我吧
* Call me *
哇喔
Wow!
小芭比 别兴奋过头了哦
Barbie, eat your heart out.
啊哈 呃
Uh… Urn…
表现自然点 好不
Just act natural.Right.
约我吧 约我吧
* Call me Call me *
亲爱的 约我吧 随时随地都约我吧
* My love, Call me, call me any, anytime *
约我吧 约我吧
* Call me Call me *
亲爱的 约我吧 约我
* My love, call me, call me…*
「请把娃娃交给新泽西洲 哈肯萨克市」
"Please deliver dolls to Caretaker's office, Forest Creek Cemetery.
「林溪公墓的守门人 致谢 蒂凡尼」
Hackensack New Jersey.Love and kisses, Tiffany"
公墓？
Cemetery?
为你的诡辩多理而约我吧
* Call me for your lover's lover's alibi *
约我吧 约我吧
* Call me Call me *
一直都在线
* On the line *
约我吧 随时随地都约我吧
* Call me, call me any, anytime *
大卫 你还记得布拉德·巴克么？
David, you remember when you were seeing Brad Barker?
哦 必须记得 唔
Oh! Vividly. Whoo!
你还很爱他 是吧？
You loved him, didn't you?
是的 很爱
Yeah, I did.
后来呢？
What happened?
他老妈发现了一封我写给他的信
His mother found a letter I'd written him.
然后暴走了 从那之后就没联系了
She freaked, and we haven't spoken since.
你看吧 杰德
You know, Jade,
春宵一刻值千金啊
we get very few chances in life to be happy.
你一定要把握好你现在的机遇啊
You gotta grab the brass ring when you can.
真他妈的磨蹭
We don't have time for this shit.
杰德 我有话要说
Jade, I need to talk to you.
嘿 杰西
Hey, Jesse.
嘿 大卫
Hey, David.
保持联络啊
I want details.
杰西 沃伦随时都会回来 如果他逮到你了
Jesse, Warren will be home any second. If he catches you…
杰德 你知道我永远都不会对你虚情假意
Jade, you know I'll never take you for granted.
- 杰西 - 你懂的 就像如果你做饭 我会洗碗一样 对不？
- Jesse… - You know, like if you'd cook, I'd do the dishes, right?
你说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
我愿意为你付出一切 一切的一切
I'd do anything for you, anything at all.
你知道的 对不？
You know that, right?
对不？
Right?
是的 是的 我知道
Yes. Yes, I know.
那嫁给我吧
Then marry me.
- 什么？- 嫁给我
- What? - Marry me.
就今晚
Tonight.
沃伦会宰了我们的
Warren would kill us.
我不在乎沃伦怎样
I don't care about Warren.
这就是我们要私奔的原因
That's why we're gonna disappear.
我们要去哪？
Where are we gonna go?
你想去哪就去哪
Anywhere you want.
好吧 那钱怎么办？
Well, what are we gonna do for money?
我有钱
I got money.
你怎么搞到的钱？
Where did you get this?
你记得我那个邻居 蒂凡尼么？
You know my neighbor, Tiffany?
她付了我500元 托我送一对娃娃给她新泽西的一个朋友
She's paying me$500 to take a couple of dolls to a friend of hers in Jersey.
杰德 送到之后还会再收到500元的
Jade, there's another $500 when we get there.
哦 妈的 杰西 那骚货想干嘛？
Oh, shit, Jesse. What has that freak gotten you into?
我不知道 也不在乎
I don't know. I don't care.
我可以贷款买套房子 找份工作
I can put a deposit on an apartment. I'll get a job.
然后供你上大学
I'll help put you through college.
我想我快吐了
I think I'm gonna throw up.
杰德 嫁给我吧
Jade, marry me.
怎么样？
What do you say?
好吧 「我愿意」
I say, "I do"
那走吧 去收拾东西
Come on. Let's get you packed.
好的
Okay.
啊哦 真浪漫啊
Aw, that's so romantic.
顶多半年 或者三个月 若她变胖的话
I give them six months, three if she gains weight.
是我
It's me.
他的车正好停在我家门口
His van is parked right in front of my house as we speak.
这家伙是谁？想干嘛？
Who the hell is this bozo? What's he doing?
捣乱我们行程的 还能干嘛
Screwing with our ride, that's what.
啊哈 管他呢 我要运动运动了
Ah, what the hell.I need the exercise.
那刀是长在你手上的么？
Were you born with that Knife super-glued onto your hand, or what?
你说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
上帝保佑 恰吉 新潮一点好不？
For God's sake, Chucky, drag yourself into the '90s.
别想什么邦德和电锯杀人狂了
Stabbings went out with Bundy and Dahmer.
你就像玛莎·斯图尔特拿着菜刀是的
You look like Martha Stewart with that thing.
谁是他妈的玛莎·斯图尔特
Who the fuck is Martha Stewart?
我的偶像
My idol.
当家里来宾客你又恰好没时间购物时
And what does Martha tell you to do
玛莎就会告诉你怎么做
when guests drop by for dinner and you haven't had time to shop
发挥你的创意
You improvise.
这个怎么样
What about…
显而易见了…
Predictable…
嗯
Hmm…
呃
Uh…
啊哈
A-ha!
谁在那了？
Who's there?
呃
Ugh!
动手
Now!
为什么看起来这么面熟呢？
Why does that look so familiar?
看到了吗？现在 这真是天才的杰作
See? Now, that's the work of a true homicidal genius.
不赖嘛 对于一个业余选手来说
Not bad, for an amateur.
妈的 他们回来了
Shit. Here they come.
真棒
Yeah!
这家伙怎么办？
What do we do with him?
我也不知道
I don't know.
玛莎·斯图尔特会怎么做？
What would Martha Stewart do?
这
Here.
过来 帮忙啊
Come on. Help me.
正帮忙呢 太重了
I am helping. He's heavy.
等等
Wait.
啊？
Huh?
怎么了？
What's the matter?
我不会粗心不锁车门吧？
I could've sworn that door was locked.
赶快吧 我们得走了
Come on. We have to go.
哦 这个
Oh, yeah!
还击吧
* Give it back *
宝贝 宝贝
* My, my *
妈的
Shit!
我好空虚
* I'm empty *
又很悲伤
* And sad *
又他妈的干嘛？
Now what?
今晚怎么样 孩子们？
How you kids doing tonight?
要去哪？
Going somewhere?
请你俩都下车 好不？
Will you both get out of the van now, please?
诺顿警员 我有个问题
Officer Norton, I have a question.
你这么跟踪我们
All this following us around…
是你的正常职务所在呢？
Is that covered by your regular salary?
还是我叔叔付钱指使你的？
Or does my uncle pay you extra?
是你叔叔
Extra.
听着 我相信你也不是坏人
Look, I'm sure you're not a bad person.
我也知道你是在履行职责而已
I know that you're just doing your job.
但是请你放过我们行不？
But couldn't you just please give us a break?
你也知道 我也希望这样
You know, I wish I could.
你们看起来也是好孩子
You seem like really nice kids.
我对你们 也没什么成见
It's nothing personal, at least on my part.
但是 是为了钱
But… The money.
你真够恶心的 闭嘴
You're disgusting.Shut up!
妈的闭嘴 不然我发誓 我会宰了你的
Shut up, or I swear to God, I'll fucking vaporize you.
啊哈
Ahh!
别激动 放松点 放松 没事的
Come on. Take it easy. Take it easy. Come here.
哦 天啊 这样的话我们哪也去不成
Oh, God. We're never gonna get away with this.
他们不会放过我们的
They're never gonna let us go.
一切都会好的
It's gonna be okay.
好不？
All right?
现在 你去路边买点吃的
Now, why don't you go get us something to eat for the road,
然后我来搞定这个尼德莱诺斯
and I'll deal with Needlenose.
- 好不？- 好吧
- All right? - Okay.
呃…
Ugh!
啊哈
Ah!
哦 真他妈的胡搞
Oh, that's bulishit!
你知道这不是我的
You know this isn't mine.
你摊上大事了 孩子
You're in a lot of trouble, kid.
现在他妈的老实呆着
Now don't you fucking move.
妈的 妈的
Shit! Shit!
这他妈的简直就是《绝命追杀令》
Figures you'd hitch us a ride with the fugitive.
打火机给我
Give me your lighter.
你要干嘛？
What are you doing?
发挥创意
Improvising.
现在 好好坐着 和大师学着点
Now, sit back and learn from the master.
金凯德警长没有回复
Chief Kincaid isn't answering.
你什么意思？「没有回复」 我就是想和他谈话
What do you mean, "He's not answering?" I just talked to him.
狗屁烂娃娃
Rude fucking doll.
杰德 快回来
Come on, Jade.
诺顿？
Norton?
你还在么？
Are you still there?
诺顿？
Norton?
拜拜
Bye!
杰西
Jesse!
杰西 杰西
Jesse! Jesse!
上车 快上车
Get in! Get in.
他们在那 快报警
There they are.Call the police.
妈的 妈的 快走
Shit. Shit. Go!
杰西 开车 快走
Jesse, drive! Go!
快走
Go!
好吧 至少你还没有忘了
Well, at least you haven't forgotten
怎么去讨好一个姑娘
how to show a girl a good time.
你刚才去哪了？
Where were you?
憋了半天就这句话？
Is that all you have to say?
那你想要我说什么？
What do you want me to say?
我以为你有话要说呢
I should think you'd have something
说说刚才那是咋回事
to say about what happened back there.
我要说 你真他妈的疯了
I got something to say. I think you're fucking crazy.
我疯了？
I'm crazy?
这就是你所说的：「你会付出一切？」
You say you'd do anything for me, and this is what I get?
等等 你感觉刚才那是我干的？
Wait a minute. You don't think that I had anything to do
- 刚才那场爆炸 - 不是么？
- with that explosion back there? - Didn't you?
不是
No.
老实说 我还觉得你有嫌疑呢
To be honest, I was thinking the same thing about you.
你怎么能那样想？
How could you think that?
你当着一群人面前说
You announced in front of a hundred people
你要宰了他
that you wanted to vaporize him.
哦 那只是说说而已
Oh, it was a figure of speech.
好吧 你刚才也是这么怀疑我的
Well, you were just as quick to accuse me.
喂 怎么个屄事？
Hello. What the fuck!
大卫 我也不知道该怎么说？
David, I don't know what to tell you.
我不知道这周围到底他妈的怎么了
I don't know what the hell is going on around here.
好吧 警方认为作案手法干净利落
Well, the cops seem to think it's all pretty cut and dried.
想想什么《闪灵杀手》《鸳鸯大盗》吧 想起来了吗？
Think of Mickey and Mallory, Bonnie and Clyde. You get the picture?
或是《闪灵杀手》《鸳鸯大盗》？
Mickey and Mallory? Bonnie and Clyde?
他们都是疯狂杀手 大卫
They were mass murderers, David.
多重杀手 确切说
Multiple murderers, actually.
他们一次杀很多人 就像电影里「邮局」的那段
Mass murders happen all at once, Like at the post office.
就像现在正火的「连环杀手」
Multiple murders are serial killings.
我不太懂 不是只死了诺顿一个吗 不是吗？
Am I missing something? Norton was just one murder, right?
警察在诺顿的车旁发现一个打火机
They found a cigarette lighter next to Norton's car.
是那个被割喉的贝利警员的
Belonged to that cop who got his throat slashed.
然后还有另一件事
And there's another thing.
杰德 你叔叔失踪了
Jade, your uncle's missing.
什么？
What?
听着 我知道这事与你俩无关
Look, I know you two had nothing to do with this.
但是或许你俩应该在他们破案之前先去自首
But maybe you should turn yourselves in until they figure it out.
大卫 你疯了嘛？谁会相信我们？
David, are you whacked? Nobody is gonna believe us.
他们会在洲界设路卡检查的
They're setting up roadblocks at the border.
你俩最好躲一躲
You two had better lay low for a while.
谢了
Thanks.
你今晚看到沃伦了么？
Did you see Warren tonight?
早上之后就没见过
Not since this morning.
- 你呢？- 也没
- Did you? - No.
（尼加拉瀑布）
∮ 我们七号大街的小屋正逐渐变冷 ∮
∮ Our little room on Seventh street is getting cold ∮
∮ 某天我在毛毯上看到了一圈图案 ∮
∮ I saw a pattern on a blanket just the other day ∮
∮ 看起来就像你扔掉的枕头 ∮
∮ It looked just like the pillow you threw away ∮
∮ 嗯 哼 ∮
∮ Uh-huh ∮
∮ 某天夜里我突然醒来 ∮
∮ I just woke up the other night ∮
∮ 现在我知道该做什么 我猜是看你去下地狱 ∮
∮ And now I know what to do I guess I'll see you in hell ∮
∮ 对吧 ∮
∮ Yeah ∮
你要干嘛？
What are you doing?
你相信我吗 杰德？
Do you trust me, Jade?
当然相信
Of course I do.
白痴啊
Sucker.
我想他们真的很般配
I think they make a cute couple.
你是否认为 就此拆散他们真的是太可惜了
And if you ask me, it'd be a shame to break 'em up,
如果你明白我的意思
if you know what I mean.
敬爱的主啊
Dearly beloved,
我们今夜齐聚于此
we are gathered here tonight
见证这对新人的结合
to celebrate the union of two people in holy matrimony.
在主的庇佑之下
And what God joins together,
让他们永不分离
let no man tear asunder.
电影与电视里的暴力镜头
Violence in movies and television…
这他妈什么屄玩意儿？
What is this shit?
无所谓
Never mind…
妈的 我死之后音乐越来越烂
Jesus, the music scene's gone to hell since I've been dead.
这才像点样儿么
That's more like it.
多么美好啊？
Isn't it beautiful?
我一直梦想着能在教堂里办一场盛大的婚礼
I always dreamed of having a big church wedding
有伴娘 蛋糕 还有报纸上的宣传照片
with bridesmaids and a cake and my picture in the paper.
不仅仅是普通的狗仔照 是漂亮的婚纱照
Not just the usual mug shot, but something really flattering.
蒂凡尼
Tiff?
都是我不好
I'm sorry.
一直都是
For everything.
呃 我想我不能这么小气了
Urn, I guess I can't corn plain.
我是说 我总想着让我们多多在一起
I rnean, I always wanted us to spend rnore tirne together,
一起旅行啊 看看世界
maybe do some traveling and see the world.
然而 现在看看我们
Well, just look at us now.
是的 人生总是充满着惊喜
Yeah. Life sure is full of surprises.
拦住他
Stop him!
宰了他
Kill him!
不论顺利挫折
For better or worse,
不论贫贱富贵
for richer or poorer,
不论健康病痛
in sickness and in health,
爱的至死不渝
till death do you part.
恭喜 你可以吻你的新娘了
Congratulations. You may now kiss the bride.
嗯？
Huh?
经典永远都是经典啊
A true classic never goes out of style.
真不错
That was good.
杰德和杰西是连环杀手的事实是真的么？
Is it true that Jesse and Jade may in fact be the serial killers
就你最近几日的侦查来看？
that you've been tracking for the past few days?
我们有一些
We have some…
这次我们无法证实
We can't confirm that at this time.
前几宗命案似乎出自一人之手
The previous murders appear to be the work of just one killer.
当然 可能是他们的一个人质
It's possible, actually, it's possible that one of them is a hostage
或者是根本就毫不知情
or simply unaware of what the other is up to.
警探？
Detective?
就目前来看 根据现有的信息
For the time being, in the absence of any other information,
这俩孩子可能是持有枪械 并且非常危险
these kids have to be considered armed and extremely dangerous.
首先 明天上午我们去送娃娃
First thing tomorrow morning, we deliver the dolls.
然后收钱
We collect our money.
我们需要钱
We're gonna need it.
哦
Oh!
不好意思 门 呃 门是开着的
Excuse me. The, uh, door was open.
我刚才不知道屋里有人
I didn't realize there was anybody in here.
拉斯 我想我们刚才订了套「总统套」
Russ! I thought we were getting a suite.
哇喔
Whoa!
这谁啊？
Who's this?
我想我们刚才订了套「总统套」
I thought we were getting a suite.
不 这是我们的房间
No. This is our room.
哦
Oh.
Oh!
拉斯
Russ!
看啊 你这一辈子看过这么可爱的东西么？
Look. Have you ever seen anything so cute in your whole life?
好棒的结婚礼物啊 她太美了
What a great idea for a wedding gift. She's beautiful.
哦
Oh.
啊 这个小家伙 长了一张只有他妈才喜欢的脸
Well, this little guy has a face only a mother could love.
嘿 我是恰吉 换做我 就会闭嘴的
Hi. I'm Chucky, and I wouldn't talk if I were you.
嘿-嘚-吼
H i-de-ho.
恰吉 我想起来了 那个好哥们娃娃
Chucky! Of course. I remember.He was a Good Guy doll.
据说会说各种脏话的
They were programmed to say all kinds of shit.
哦
Ooh.
妈的 我真不喜欢它
Well, I don't like him at all.
知道吗 你们真是郎才女貌的一对
You know, you two really make a delicious-looking couple.
嘿 戴安 你认为呢？
Hey, Diane, don't you think?
哦 当然
Oh, absolutely.
我是说 想想他们孩子会是什么样？
I mean, imagine what their children are gonna look like, huh?
听着 天有点晚了 然后
Listen, it's getting late, and…
那么 你们今晚要干嘛？嗯？
So, what are you guys up to tonight? Hmm?
这是我们的新婚之夜
It's our wedding night.
那么 那你们还看毛电视啊？
Well, so what are you watching TV for?
恩 你看 我们也是新婚之夜
Well, you see, it's our wedding night as well,
这样多完美啊
which is what makes this just so perfect.
你知道别人怎么说么？「人越多 越热闹」
You know what they say?"The more, the merrier."
好吧 好吧 不行
Okay, yeah. No.
你知道吗？我们很累了 想早点睡觉
You know what? We're really tired. Gotta get to bed early.
好吧 好吧 我们就在隔壁
Okay, well, we'll be right next door.
好吧
Okay.
那个小偷贱人
That thieving slut.
她不配带那颗戒指
She doesn't deserve to wear that ring.
敬我门
To us.
哦 拉斯 让我歇会吧
Oh, Russ, give me a break.
我们正儿八经的在度蜜月 记得不？
We are, technically, on our honeymoon, remember?
是的 好吧 是你要来这的 不是我
Yeah, well, it was your idea to come here, not mine.
和你说过我们在度假中心捞的要更多
I told you we'd have seen more action at Club Med.
好啦 既然来了 就好好干吧
Come on, we're here. Let's make the best of it.
哦
Ohh!
就这样 宝贝 来吗 对 来吗
Yeah, baby, come on. Yeah. Come on.
呃？
Huh?
爱死你了
I love you.
我很早之前就该这么做
I should have asked you this a long time ago.
蒂凡尼 愿意做我的新娘么？
Tiffany, will you be my bride?
哦 恰吉
Oh, Chucky.
愿意 愿意
Yes. Yes.
啊
Ah!
哦
Oh!
恰吉
Chucky.
你哭什么？
Why are you crying?
我在婚礼上都会哭
I always cry at weddings.
哦 天啊 我还会哭
Oh, my God.I'm crying.
我想知道 其他器官还管用不？
I wonder if all the plumbing works.
好吧 我不知道你怎么样 但是我已经在升国旗了
Well, I don't know about you, but I'm starting to feel like Pinocchio here.
哦
Ohh!
我的构造完全没问题 你知道的
I am anatomically correct, you know.
哦
Ohh!
等等 等等
Wait. Wait.
什么？干嘛？什么事？
What? What? What?
你有乳胶（套套）吗？
Have you got a rubber?
我有乳胶（套套）吗？
Have I got a rubber?
是的
Yeah.
- 亲爱的 - 干嘛？
- Tiff! - What?
看看我 我浑身都是乳胶（套套）
Look at me. I'm all rubber.
哦 好吧 等等 我还以为你是塑胶的
Oh, that's right. Wait.I thought you were plastic.
- 亲爱的 - 干嘛？
- Tiff! - What?
- 吻我 - 好的
- Kiss me. - Okay.
喂？大卫 是我
Hello? David, it's me.
杰德
Jade!
- 你们在哪？- 尼加拉
- Where are you? - Niagara.
汽车蜜月旅馆
The Honeymoon Sweets motel,
还有 相信我这比听起来还要糟糕
which, believe me, is even worse than it sounds.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
不好 我结婚了
No. I'm married.
那还不好？
Is that bad?
我真的好害怕
I'm really scared.
我想 可能是他干的 大卫
I think, maybe he did it, David.
我想杰西可能已经彻底的迷失了
I think Jesse has totally lost it.
天啊
Jesus.
我该怎么办？
What should I do?
你确定么？
Are you sure?
非常确定
Pretty sure.
那你必须去警局
Then you've got to go to the police.
我做不到
I don't think I can.
我还爱着他
I still love him.
有什么问题么？
Is that wrong?
等会
Hold on a second.
喂？大卫 是我
Hello? David, it's me.
嘿 杰西
Hey, Jesse.
抱歉这么晚给你打电话
I'm sorry to call you so late.
有麻烦了 是杰德
I got a problem. It's Jade.
听我说 去警局
Listen to me. Go to the police.
现在 在没人受伤之前
Now, before somebody else gets hurt.
呦 吼 有人吗？
Yoo-hoo! Anybody here?
房间打扫
Housekeeping!
有人吗？房间打扫
Hello? Housekeeping.
在这玩的开心点
Joy to be here.
好吧 哦 我
Okay. Oh, my…
果然新婚
Newlyweds.
你们玩的都啥花样啊？
What the heck went on here?
我不能这样
I can't do this.
什么？
What?
我不能和你一起走 杰西
I can't go with you, Jesse.
分手吧
Not anymore.
哦 你能先说出来可真是解脱
Oh, man, I'm glad you said that first.
为什么？
Why?
杰德 我受不了了
Jade, this is too much for me.
我爱你 我会一直爱着你
I love you. I will always love you.
但是我的忍耐是有限度的
But there is a limit to how much I can take.
你能不能别在说「我是个疯子」之类的话了？
Would you please stop talking to me like I'm the one who's crazy?
你才是疯子呢 你才是疯狂杀手呢
You're the crazy one! You're the mass murderer!
你是说多重杀手
You mean multiple murderer.
- 那你算是承认了？- 不 我没有
- So you admit it? - No, I don't!
我真他妈忍不了了
I can't take this shit anymore.
好吧 既然你们两个立场都那么坚定
Anyway, the thing that struck me was how sure you both sounded.
我想 只有三个可能
And to me, that meant one of three things.
一是有人说谎 二是你们脑子让驴踢了
One of you is lying, both of you are whacko,
三是你们都错了
or both of you are wrong.
还有我比任何人都了解你们俩
Add to that the fact that I know you both better than anybody else,
你俩就连一只苍蝇都不忍伤害
and I've never seen either of you so much as hurt a fly,
然后结论就是
and I've concluded that what we have here
这是一个天大的误会
is a terrible misunderstanding.
你们闻到什么怪味没？
Do you guys smell something in here?
好 你们吵架的原因是什么
Okay, for the sake of argument,
不是你干的 也不是我干的？
if it wasn't you, and it wasn't me,
那么谁会去想杀掉沃伦和尼德莱诺斯呢？
then who else would want to kill Warren and Needlenose?
还有那对夫妻
And those people from last night.
你脑袋进水了？沃伦死了吗？他只是失踪了
You're assuming Warren's dead.He's only missing.
你是在说沃伦
You're suggesting that Warren…
是的 为什么不能？
Yes! Why not?
我打赌他比你们还要神经质
I'd buy him as a psychopath before either of you two.
噗 啥玩意这么臭
Pooh! Something really stinks in here.
我告诉过你别在这里乱扔袜子了
I told you not to leave your dirty socks back there.
宝贝 这可不是袜子味
Honey, this ain't no dirty socks.
- 我真是个大白痴 - 我也是
- I feel like such an idiot.- Me, too.
我是说 我竟然会相信你会去杀人
I mean, I can't believe I actually thought that you could kill someone.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm so sorry.
大卫 我们真的不能离开你
David, what would we do without you?
你什么意思 「离开我」
What do you mean, "Without me?"
我是说你让我们都清醒了 我们欠你一次
I mean you set us straight.We owe you one.
你真是个好哥们 最好的
You're a good friend. The best.
停车 马上停车
Pull over! Pull over now!
大卫 怎么了 哥们 有话好好说
David, come on, buddy, it's me. Come on, let's talk this over.
- 我不是你哥们 - 我操 大卫
- I'm not your buddy. - Fuck, David!
把枪放下来
Please put the gun down.
为嘛？那样你们就能把我也杀了？
Why? So you can kill me too?
我们没杀过人
We didn't kill anybody.
哦 你们真行 真行啊 差点骗过我
Oh, you're good. You're good! You even had me fooled.
你说啥呢？
What are you talking about?
这个
This!
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch!
大卫 不是我做的 是她做的
David, I didn't do it. She did it!
我从没有
I would never…
闭嘴
Shut up!
嘿 救命 这边
Hey, help! Over here!
- 统统不许动 - 哦 天啊
- Nobody move! - Oh, my God!
不要
No!
这样也行？
That works too?
妈的把车开起来 快 快 快
Get this heap of shit moving! Now! Now! Now!
（您现在已经到达 新泽西洲 花园之洲）
我想关于这点你俩一定满脑子问号吧
I imagine at this point you two must have a lot of questions.
你知道我们是谁吧？
You do know who I am?
恰吉 还有这是蒂凡尼
Chucky. And this is Tiffany.
我们以前见过 对吧 心肝？
I believe we've already met, haven't we, sweetface?
那么 你们怎么变成的娃娃？
So, how did you end up like this?
这个 说来话长啊
Well, it's a long story.
确实啊
It sure is.
实际上 如果拍成电影
In fact, if it was a movie,
至少能拍个三四集
it would take three or four sequels just to do it justice.
你们要拿我们怎么办？
What are you gonna do with us?
问的真有意思
Funny you should ask.
娃娃身体还好
These bodies are okay.
但是他们就像租来的房子
But they're like apartments that we're just renting.
但是现在我们要改变现状
But now we're movin' on up.
找个好地段
Like George and Weezie.
买一套房子
And we're looking to buy.
当人们说起房产 总是说到
And you know what they say about real estate.
地段 地段 地段
Location, location, location.
你们几个家伙 来的正好 但是来的不巧
Well, you guys are definitely in the right place at the wrong time.
紧急特殊报道
This is a WEBH special report.
杰西和杰德的案件变得越来越诡异
The Jesse and Jade case keeps getting weirder and weirder.
在两个凶案现场
Fin gerprints discovered at two separate crime scenes
都采集到了查尔斯·李·雷的指纹
have been identified as belonging to Charles Lee Ray,
在1988年于玩具店被击毙的连环杀手
the notorious serial killer gunned down in 1988.
警方计划今日前往新泽西洲 哈肯萨克市林溪公墓
Now police confirm that Ray's corpse will be exhumed
掘出查尔斯·李·雷的尸体
from a Hackensack, New Jersey cemetery sometime today.
- 什么？- 恰吉 洛阿神之心
- What? - Chucky, the Heart of Damballa!
- 我知道 - 该怎么办？该怎么办？
- I know! - WhaVII we do? WhaVII we do?
闭嘴 让我想想 行不？
Shut up! Just let me think, okay?
首先得先换辆车
First we gotta get some new wheels.
半径500米内的条子都能发现这辆车
Every cop within 500 miles is looking for this van.
我们需要一辆不显眼 但是很拉风的车
We need something inconspicuous, but with a little style.
（向东46公里 欢迎光临哈肯萨克）
稳住 宝贝 免得又刺到你的眼睛
Hold still, honey, or I'm gonna poke you in the eye again.
是的 我相信我一定会迷死人了
Yes. I believe I'm going to look absolutely ravishing.
抱歉了
Excuse me.
你的瑞士肉丸天下第一 宝贝
Nobody makes Swedish meatballs like you, babe.
- 超赞 - 谢谢 大宝贝
- Peachy! - Thanks, honey pot.
我希望你能留着点肚子
I hope you left room for dessert.
我会的 小宝贝
You know it, pooky.
知道吗 早知道结婚这么快活的话
You know, if I had known that marriage was such a great gig,
我也不会拖了这么久
I would never have waited this long to tie the knot.
从某方面来讲 她不太会收拾屋子 是吧？
On the other hand, she's not much of a housekeeper, is she?
- 蒂凡尼？- 啊？
- Tiff? - Huh?
那些盘子他们不会自己洗好的 知道吧
Those dishes aren't gonna wash themselves, you know.
你给做饭就很不错了
You were nice enough to cook for him.
他好歹也洗个碗吧
The least he could do is wash the dish.
哦
Oh!
你干嘛啊？
What are you doing?
玛莎·斯图尔特会怎么说？
What would Martha Stewart say?
去他妈的玛莎·斯图尔特
Fuck Martha Stewart.
玛莎·斯图尔特只配来亲我的塑胶屁股
Martha Stewart can kiss my shiny plastic butt.
我他妈的在灶前忙来忙去
Here I am slaving away over a hot stove,
做饼干 做瑞士肉丸 都为了什么？
making cookies, making Swedish meatballs, and for what?
为了一个不会欣赏我的臭男人
For a man who doesn't appreciate me.
为了一个连盘子都不洗的臭男人
For a man who can't even wash one fucking dish.
为了一个连男人都算不上的男人
For a man who isn't even a man at all where it counts,
如果你明白我说的
if you get my drift.
相信我 亲爱的
Take it from me, honey.
塑胶是无法取代木棒的
Plastic is no substitute for a nice hunk of wood.
昨天晚上她可没这么抱怨
I didn't hear her complaining last night.
那些需要木棒的家伙 确切说是电动跳蛋
Any guy would need a hunk of plastic, probably battery-operated,
来达到自己的高潮
to get a reaction out of you in bed.
还有
And by the way,
你他妈的从哪学的这种烤这种屎饼干？
where the hell did you learn to bake?
你竟敢这么对我说话
How dare you speak to me that way!
是你起的头
You started it!
我没有
I did not!
不
No…
哇哦
Whoa!
杰西？杰西？醒醒 求你了 哦 天啊
Jesse? Jesse, please.Please. Oh, God.
杰西？
Jesse?
让我出去
Get me out of here!
你个贱人
You bitch!
杰德
Jade!
快点
Hurry!
- 快 快 快走 - 不能扔下你
- Go, go, go! - Not without you!
我随后就到
I'll be right behind you!
嘿 美女
Hey, beautiful.
啊哈
Aah!
杰德
Jade!
继续走
Move it!
（林溪公墓）
（查尔斯·李·雷之墓 卒于1988年）
下去 快点
Get down there. Move!
打开棺材 杰德
Open the coffin, Jade.
- 快点 - 很快了 你这个混蛋小魔星
- Hurry up.- I'm trying, you fucking midget!
呃 真是惨不忍睹啊
Ugh! You really didn't need to see that.
把护身符给我
Give me the amulet.
哦
Oh!
贱人 你弄断了我的脖子
Bitch! You broke my neck.
放了她
Let her go.
先放了杰德
Let Jade go first.
过去
Get moving.
杰德？待会见
And Jade? See you real soon.
滚过去
Get out of here.
好男人难道都死光了么？
Why can't I ever get it on with the real good guys?
你真是幸运的女孩
You're a lucky girl.
抱紧我 恰吉
Catch me, Chucky.
呃…
Ugh!
啊哈
Aah!
哦 天啊 不
Oh, God, no!
天啊 不要
God, no!
拔出来
Pull it out.
我来搞定
I'll take that.
好戏登场了
It's show time.
[咒语]
我祈求你 赐予我力量吧
Give me the power, I beg of you!
[咒语]
搞定了
This is it.
我爱你 恰吉
I love you, Chucky.
我知道
I know.
我们属于彼此了 永远
We belong together, forever.
吻我
Kiss me.
哈
Hah!
为什么？
Why?
哦 恰吉 瞧瞧我们
Oh, Chucky, look at us.
难道你不懂么？
Don't you see?
我们非死不可
We belong dead.
再见了 亲爱的
Goodbye, darling.
地狱里在相见
I'll see you in hell.
我妈妈总是对我说
My mother always told me
爱会让人自由
love would set me free.
从我刀上滚开
Get off my knife.
把手举起来
Let me see your hands!
把枪放下 放下
Drop the gun! Drop it!
让我上去 让我上去 让我上去 让我上去
Let me out! Let me out! Let me out! Let me out!
哇喔
Whoa.
别动
Don't move!
来开枪啊
Go ahead and shoot.
我会复活的 我总是会复活的
I'll be back.I always come back.
但是死亡真他妈的痛苦
But dying is such a bitch.
这种事是没人会相信的 你们懂么？
No one's ever gonna believe this.You know that?
那我们会怎么样？
What's gonna happen to us?
普莱斯顿 是的 我在这了
Preston. Yeah, I'm here now.
恐怕我们的清单上又多了一具尸体
I'm afraid we've got another corpse to add to the list.
杰西和杰德？
Jesse and Jade?
妈的 不是他们干的
Hell, they didn't do it.
赶紧把法医喊过来
Just get forensics down here.
你们绝不会相信这种操蛋事的
You're never gonna fucking believe this.
对的
Right.
你俩回家 别乱跑
You two go on home. And stay put.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
哦
Ooh.
天啊
Jesus.
我了个大操 我了个去
Goddamn! Son of a bitch!
我操
Holy…
贱人 妈的
Bitch! Jesus!